# German Huayhua Condori

# Software Engineer - Full Stack Developer

yhermmany@gmail.com

github.com/hcgerman

inkedin.com/in/hcgerman

## **About me**

I'm software developer with experience in web development. I have worked for more than 4 years in technology companies in backend and full stack developer roles. I am responsible and kind. I consider myself a communicative person willing to work in a team, efficient in the achievements, goals and objectives set by the company.

# Relevant Experience

#### Full Stack Developer @ Notus SpA

Oct 2021 - Present // Santiago, Chile

- ▶ Write modern, performant, and robust code for a diverse array of client and internal projects
- ▶ Development of project with .NET Core and Django.
- Development of python modules with geospatial data like vector data and raster data and Arcgis integration.
- ▶ Implement flows with Argo Workflows.
- Design and implement well-encapsulated external and internal architectures based on Docker and Kubernetes in the AWS cloud.
- ▶ Build CI/CD pipeline with tools like Gitlab CI and Github Actions.
- ▶ Communicate and collaborate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, clients, and stakeholders on a daily basis.

#### Backend Developer @ tuGerente

April 2020 - September 2021 // Santa Cruz, Bolivia

- ▶ Development of ERP system, python modules, Django projects, Node JS projects and React JS projects.
- ▶ Design and development of distributed applications using sockets and web services.
- Dockerization of applications.
- ▶ Work with a variety of different languages, frameworks, and content management systems such as JavaScript, React, Vue, Node.js, Express JS, Python, Django, Shopify, WordPress, etc.
- ▶ Development of automated tests with TDD.
- ▶ Integrations with external services such as Shopify, Woocommerce, Pedidos Ya, among others.

#### Full Stack Developer @ Ticketeg S.R.L.

February 2018 - March 2020 // Santa Cruz, Bolivia

- ▶ Development of payment platform and event management system.
- ▶ Design and development of web applications using Django and Ruby on Rails.
- ▶ Development of automated tests with TDD.
- ▶ Design and development of mobile applications with React Native projects on Android and IOS.
- ▶ Implementation of Web Services such as SOAP, RESTful and Graphql.

## Skills

#### **Programming Languages**

Python, Ruby, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, C#

#### **Libraries & Frameworks**

Diango, Ruby on Rails, React JS, React Native, Next.js, Express, Jekyll, .Net Core

#### **Tools & Platforms**

Git, Heroku, Amazon Web Services (EC2, Route 53, S3), Docker, Kubernetes, Argo Workflows, Linux Servers, Node JS + Express

#### **Education**

# **CBA** (Centro Boliviano Americano)

2019 - Present // Santa Cruz, BO English Course - Intermediate Level

# **UAGRM (Universidad Autonoma** Gabriel Rene Moreno)

2018 // Santa Cruz, BO **Business Systems Management** 

2013 - 2018 // Santa Cruz, BO Bachelor of Computer Engineering

#### Interests

Reading, traveling, attend online and face-to-face training, go fishing, watch movies with the family.